<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Apollon</title><subtitle>A minimal, responsive, and powerful Jekyll theme for presenting professional writing.</subtitle> <updated>2022-08-12T06:54:31+08:00</updated> <author> <name>apolloni4n</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 apolloni4n </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>I have too many words I can't assemble for you</title><link href="/posts/Poetry/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I have too many words I can't assemble for you" /><published>2022-08-11T09:56:00+08:00</published> <updated>2022-08-12T05:28:26+08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Poetry/</id> <content src="/posts/Poetry/" /> <author> <name>apollon</name> </author> <category term="poetry" /> <category term="soul" /> <category term="art" /> <summary> This post is within a serie of my poetic inspirations Titles —If there is any God Love I d just want u to know, crystallized FLOOD How u were beautifully made by god I believe he has taken every single moment to draw You, As if he s gonna die tomorrow With love and enthusiasm he made your eyes And with an angelic voice he filled your throat I hope with a whiter color than white itself he paint... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Thoughts I</title><link href="/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Thoughts I" /><published>2022-08-11T09:56:00+08:00</published> <updated>2022-08-11T09:56:00+08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy-2/</id> <content src="/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy-2/" /> <author> <name>apollon</name> </author> <category term="Thoughts" /> <category term="meaning" /> <category term="soul" /> <category term="spirituality" /> <category term="love" /> <summary> Thoughts -I listened to a podcast of “L’heure philo” and they’re like walking is good for thinking and most Greek philosophs were doing it inattentivally and they don’t mention it but they do it for a long time or hours, Nietzsche thinks that any idea should be out with a physical effort (I don’t know how to say it in english but i feel it, Actually any idea from Nietzsche I feel it rather than... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Ingmar Bergmann</title><link href="/posts/Ingmar-Bergmann/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Ingmar Bergmann" /><published>2022-08-11T09:56:00+08:00</published> <updated>2022-08-12T05:28:26+08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Ingmar-Bergmann/</id> <content src="/posts/Ingmar-Bergmann/" /> <author> <name>apollon</name> </author> <category term="films" /> <category term="cinema" /> <category term="soul" /> <category term="art" /> <summary> This post is within a serie of my poetic cinema inspirations Titles —Ingmar Bergmann (July 14, 1918 — July 30, 2007) Film “No form of art goes beyond ordinary consciousness as film does, straight to our emotions, deep into the twilight room of the soul.” — Ingmar Bergman Peace Be within you! Be careful of false beliefs and get hydrated and loved! </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Nietzsche I</title><link href="/posts/Nietzsche-I/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Nietzsche I" /><published>2022-08-10T09:56:00+08:00</published> <updated>2022-08-12T05:28:26+08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Nietzsche-I/</id> <content src="/posts/Nietzsche-I/" /> <author> <name>apollon</name> </author> <category term="Philosophy" /> <summary> This post is within a serie of my philosophical inspirations… Titles — A philosoph who refuses to be a considered as one. The great man of all time Why I love Nietzsche the reason I love Nietzsche (While I disagree with some of what he has to say), is because a philosopher’s power lies in the consistency of their voice. No other philosopher has so consistently, made me question the very founda... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Music and poems I</title><link href="/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Music and poems I" /><published>2022-08-09T09:56:00+08:00</published> <updated>2022-08-09T09:56:00+08:00</updated> <id>/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy/</id> <content src="/posts/Music-and-poems-I-copy/" /> <author> <name>apollon</name> </author> <category term="music" /> <category term="meaning" /> <category term="soul" /> <category term="spirituality" /> <category term="love" /> <summary> This post is within a serie of my music inspirations, the music that penetrates my very soul always, never disappoints, I keep discovering new styles and genres for ecstasy and eargasm, but for meaning too. Titles —Max Richter Music Inspiration Dawn How enduring, how we need durability. The sky before sunrise is soaked with light. Rosy colour tints buildings, bridges, and the Seine. I was he... </summary> </entry> </feed>
